

Purushottam Thapa Magar

E-mail § Purushottam.ThapaMagar@gmail.com Website § http://mun-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

Phone § 0443622069

Address § Siltapellonkuja 2 R 142, Helsinki - 00740, Finland

PERSONAL STATEMENT

As a recent graduate from Metropolia University of Applied Sciences with Bachelor degree in Media Engineering, I have undertaken couple projects withing leading organizations such as Dooxe Oy and Metropolia UAS. These placements have enabled me to develop not only specific web-development industry experience, but also a valuable and transferable skill set in this fast-paced sector. During placement in Dooxe, I worked as a web-developer contributing to a web-service Korjausurakka.fi and did my own research leading to the Bachelor's Thesis. Furthermore, on both placement I practiced agile software development methods. Utilising excellent communication skills, I developed and maintained successful working relationships with all the staff on both occasions.

OBJECTIVE

Looking to secure a position in a web-development organization, where I can bring immediate and strategic value and develop current skill set further.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dooxe Oy, Helsinki

June 2012 — September 2012

Web developer

- Performed server side coding using PHP.
- Used HTML and CSS for developing client-side.
- Managed Mysql database.
- used Scrum in distributed software development.

Metropolia University of Applied Sciences

Sep 2011 — Dec 2011

Back End Developer/iOS developer

- Used Scrum as a software development methodology.
- Created back-end of an iPhone application using PHP.
- Managed Mysql Database.
- Did iOS Programming.

Own Practice Projects

Jan 2013 — Present

Web developer

I have been working and practicing in my own projects since 2013. One of them being 'Shareitloud', which is a

Purushottam Thapa Magar

Link: http://shareitloud.herokuapp.com/

KEY SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- PHP
- ASP.NET
- HTML and CSS
- SASS, Bourbon framework
- Drupal
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Ajax
- Scrum
- Software Testing
- Test Driven Development

EDUCATION

Degree Programme in Media Engineering

Metropolia University of Applied Sciences

Graduated on 25th October, 2013.

August 2009 — October 2013

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Nepalese: Native English: Fluent Finnish: Basic

REFERENCES

Mr. Kari Aaltonen of Metropolia University of Applied Sciences.

Email: Kari.Aaltonen@metropolia.fi

Phone: +358 405512891

Purushottam Thapa Magar